♪ It seems today that all you see ♪
♪ Is violence in movies and sex on TV ♪
♪ But where are those
good old-fashioned values ♪
♪ On which we used to rely? ♪
♪ Lucky there's a family guy ♪
♪ Lucky there's a man
who positively can do ♪
♪ All the things that make us ♪
♪ Laugh and cry ♪
♪ He's... a... Fam... ily... Guy! ♪
Wide open in the end zone.
Touchdown Patriots!
Beautiful pass by Tom Brady.
Yeah, Brady!
He's awesome.
I can't believe Gisele
gets to sleep with him.
I wish I was a supermodel.
Hey, it's a commercial.
Jerome, switch over to the RedZone.
Screw that, I say we
put on the BoneZone.
- What's that?
- Oh, it's awesome.
They show every sex scene on TV
without all the boring
dialogue and plot.
Okay, once again,
nothing is happening on Homeland,
but over on Masters
of Sex, Lizzie Caplan
is hooked up to electrodes
and getting it from a guy
who sounds American, but probably isn't.
Hey, we're gonna split the screens now
because my producer is
telling me on Game of Thrones
we got a malnourished
Albino plowing a girl
in a tub as he names dragons.
Oh, there's a Bone Zone
alert for Girls,
which we'll ignore,
'cause it's Gabby Hoffmann
Donald Ducking it.
Last time we went to that,
we lost a lot of subscribers,
and we're keeping
an eye on The Knick.
We don't want to bring
you dead boobs,
but if they're alive,
we'll get you over there.
Ah, crap.
It's almost 3:00. I
got to get out of here.
For what? It's Sunday.
Eh, the airline's making
us all attend a seminar
about what do to if
someone flies a drone
into your flight path.
Yeah, I hear that kind
of obnoxious behavior
is very big right now in the
dangerous idiot community.
Really? I didn't see that
in the newsletter this month.
Just a big article about how to
tailgate a speeding fire truck
to get places faster.
Wait till they
get to the golf course
and find out there's no fire.
No, It's a serious problem.
Nowadays any moron
could just order a drone online.
- Oh.
- There's no regulation.
- Oh!
- And most of them have cameras
so people can spy on whoever they want
and invade their privacy.
Oh!
Peter, are you ordering
a drone right now?
You bet your ass I am.
Owning a drone is gonna be a blast.
Even more fun than when
I had breakfast in bread.
Hi, Lois. It's a great morning,
no matter how you slice it.
Yeah, I don't know what this is Peter,
but we're four months
behind on our mortgage.
Well, that's odd.
It's not like we're
short on dough.
I'm taking the kids and
I'm staying at my parents'
for a while.
That's the yeast of my concerns.
Ah, Brian, you finally made it.
I'm having a tea party. Sit down.
Yeah, you texted me, like, 80 times.
Look, Stewie, I don't
have time to sip air
and pretend to eat a
wooden hamburger patty.
Yeah? Tell me why you don't have time.
All right, I have time.
And there's nothing pretend about this.
Real tea, real milk,
and the best honey you'll
ever taste in your whole life.
Wow, this is good.
Where'd you buy the honey?
I didn't, I'm raising bees.
You're raising bees?
Like-like a beekeeper?
Yup, Mom missed soccer registration,
so this is my weekends.
Mmm, I got to say, you're good at it.
You know, you could
probably sell this stuff.
Really? You think it's that good?
Yeah, plus it's local.
It's straight from the hive.
People at farmers' markets
would go nuts for this.
You know, you could probably
charge, like, $20, $30 a jar.
Oh, now I'm excited about this, Brian.
I feel like an eighth
grader who just had sex.
So, you go all the way?
Oh, yeah.
I'm gonna need some proof.
Hmm, how can I prove it?
Maybe with Father O'Leary's briefs.
- Oh!
- The king.
He said he loved me.
All right, time to take flight.
Drone of Arcadia.
Oh, Amber Tamblyn.
I love that show.
Now married to David Cross.
Can I have a turn? I want a turn.
No.
Hey, does Cleveland have a bald spot?
Hey, what's this do?
Check it out, Here comes a hawk.
Uh-oh.
What's happening?
Ah, no!
I don't think this is consensual!
Look at that pervert
squirrel just watching.
Oh, crap, it's busted.
And I bet it's completely traumatized.
I wasn't traumatized actually.
It was planned.
Part of the games we play.
I've been a bad drone.
Peter, you've been knocking a while.
I don't think anyone's in there.
Yeah, look at all this mail.
Maybe he's on vacation or something.
Oh, my God, he's dead!
And his face and earlobes are missing.
Oh, that's a relief.
It's just the cat that
ate his face and ears off.
So, Brian, this is my hive.
Now, how many bees do
you think are in here?
I don't know, a-a million?
No, it's 4,000.
Now that seems like nothing
because of your idiot million guess.
All right, now, if
you're going to sell honey
at the farmers' market,
you need to practice.
So you be the salesman,
and I'll be the customer.
Ooh, what do we have here?
Uh, honey.
Like the sign says.
I find your attitude cavalier.
May I speak to your manager?
Stewie, come on.
I'm sorry, is there a problem here?
I was just in the back
and I heard a commotion.
- How do we have a back?
- I simply came here
to enquire about honey
and your employee spoke to
me loudly and with profanity.
Stewie, this is ridiculous.
Brian, please, I trust that
this handsome young customer
knows what he's talking about.
Oh, my, and I thought only
bees pour on the honey.
I'm going inside.
So, are you from around here?
No I'm just in town for the
John Singer Sargent exhibit
at the museum. Really?
I've been looking for
an excuse to go again.
Well, looks like I won't
need that audio tour.
Great. Give me one minute.
Let me text my fianc├йe.
Your what?
That was Bonnie.
She said they already
sold the house behind us.
Poor Mr. Seigel.
What the hell is that?
Yeah, that party bus is awesome.
Yeah, let's go, let's go.
- Here we go, baby.
- Yeah!
Oh, God, please don't let
that be our new neighbors.
- What is it?
- Some kind of crazy van
with the number 87 on the side.
87?
That's not a van, Lois,
that's a party bus.
Rob Gronkowski's party bus!
Who's that?
Only the star tight end
of the New England Patriots
and America's most athletic Polish.
Did you guys see?
Oh, my God, that was Rob Gronkowski.
Am I running?
Is this what running is?
I hate it.
What's up, butt munchers?
That's us! He called us butt munchers!
We're butt munchers!
All right, time to Gronk
a dump in my new house.
Oh. My. God!
Our new neighbor is Gronk.
Hey, I'm your new mailman.
Former star of The Incredible
Hulk, Lou Ferrigno.
On any other day that
would be so exciting.
Please give me my mail and go.
What the hell are you doing?
I wanted to bring over
something to welcome Gronk
to the neighborhood. So I
scraped all the cool ranch
off of 15 bags of Doritos.
You're bringing him a bowl of powder?
Yeah, I thought he could
eat it by the fistful
or rub it on his balls.
Peter, I don't know what
you're so excited about.
Rob Gronkowski is probably the
worst neighbor we could ask for.
You know he's gonna be
partying day and night.
It's not like it's that tasty
piece of ass, Julian Edelman.
Now there's a Patriot
you can get excited about.
I know he's a wide receiver,
but if he's giving, I'm taking.
I'll take it all.
I'll take it wherever.
Ah!
Anyway,
go suck up to your big dumb monster.
I'll be here hooking the
"G" to thoughts of Edelman.
So, what'd you get him, Cleveland?
Oreo middles.
Whoa, four standing dogs?
No, we're people, sir.
Um, Mr. Gronk? I'm Peter Griffin.
I live in the house behind yours.
We wanted to welcome
you to the neighborhood.
Awesome!
Ha-ha, he spiked it.
I was hoping he would do that.
My eyes!
Hey, you guys seem great.
You want to come in and
eat pizza standing up?
- Uh, yeah.
- Cool.
You mind if I call you all Grover?
I don't like learning names.
Yeah, sure, that'd be sweet.
Well, come on in, Grover.
He knows my name!
Oh, my God, you guys, having
Gronk here is gonna be the best.
Kind of like those years when
it was just Marley and me.
Hey, my dog's chewing
up that thing I need.
Hey, my dirty dog's jumping
in the neighbor's pool.
Wait, Marley, don't shake your wet fur
in the middle of this fancy party.
I'm gonna lay down these
work blueprints on the floor
and I sure hope you don't walk
across them with muddy paws.
Marley!
Aw, my nightmare dog is dead.
Marley and me.
Workout room, kegerator cellar,
another workout room,
and over here's a room
that's just got a lit candle
on a bale of hay.
I-Is that just 'cause of the danger?
That's exactly why.
My dumb wife won't let
me have a room like that.
Do you have a wife?
What's going on?
Let's go check out the hot tub.
Check it out, my hot tub
is filled with coffee.
Grab a donut, go to town!
Sponsored by Dunkin' Donuts.
And the pool is filled
with my favorite food:
soup with little shapes in it.
Sponsored by Campbell Soup.
Oh, alphabet soup is my favorite, too.
What's a "albaphet"?
Nothing. What you said is not anything.
And check out the shower!
Ultra Sunrise Monster Energy Drink.
Sponsored by Monster Energy Drink.
Why do you keep saying what
things are sponsored by?
My manager said if I don't,
I won't go to heaven.
Sponsored by SMS Audio
Sweatproof Sport Headphones.
Well, you were right,
the farmers' market is wonderful.
You've got your yoga pants moms,
you got your mixed-race
kids riding a pony,
a confused Jerome...
What is this?
A vegetable parking lot?
Now, remember to tell customers
that this honey is farm-to-table.
We're not a restaurant,
that doesn't make any sense.
Doesn't have to.
Say anything-to-anything,
people lose their minds.
Just so you know,
this is all grass-to-bottle.
- Ooh!
- I know, right?
That'll be $68.
Is this a superfood?
Total superfood. Full of GMOs.
GMOs are bad.
No GMOs whatsoever.
Amazing.
Wow, this is great,
we've only been here an hour
and we're almost totally sold out.
Yes, I didn't see that coming.
Just like Dan Cortese
didn't see the end of the '90s coming.
Three...
two...
one...
Happy New Year!
Dan Cortese was the only
thing in the entire world
affected by Y2K.
Grovers, you made it!
Here, have a beer.
Thanks.
Hey, Gronk, you know, there's something
I always wanted to ask you.
When you know you have single coverage,
do you give a hand signal to Brady,
or is it just eye contact?
I don't know,
want to see me dance?
Well, no, I ask because sometimes
you're being covered by a little guy,
and then you and Brady'll
look at each other and...
A-Am I... am I supposed to touch you?
What... what am I...
what am I doing here?
Oh, I'm sorry, bro.
What was the question?
I ju... I just want to know if
you and Brady have, like, a...
Like, a secret hand signal or something.
Whoa, that is top secret,
but lean in and I'll tell you.
How rude.
Hey, want to meet my family?
These are my brothers.
Actually, one of them is my dad,
I'm not sure which.
Probably the gray-haired one
with the whiskey-face sunburn?
Oh, it's an honor to meet you, sir.
You must be very proud.
Hell yeah.
I think every dad's dream
is taking his son's sloppy seconds.
Is your mom here, too?
They don't have a mom.
My ex-wife raised them,
God bless her, but genetically,
they're a product of me
blammin' onto a side of beef.
All right, since we sold out so fast,
we've got to make these
bees more productive,
get them to make more honey.
How are we gonna do that?
Steroids, Brian.
This here is the same stuff
that turned Barry Bonds' head
into a prize-winning squash.
Okay. Well, how much are
we supposed to give them?
Hmm.
It says this is enough for a horse, so,
I don't know, how many bees is a horse?
Well, you can't fit a horse in this box,
so I'd just use the whole thing.
That makes sense.
Barry Bonds says that's
too much steroids.
Time for bed, Barry.
God, they're still going?
Peter, this is exactly what
I told you would happen!
Not so much fun anymore, is it?
Oh, thank God,
maybe they're wrapping it up.
Damn it, I can't take anymore!
He is the worst neighbor ever.
You won't believe what he did yesterday.
Hey, Grover, catch!
Uh, listen, Gronk, um,
it's gettin' kind of late.
Don't you think maybe it's
time to call it a night?
Yeah, sure.
Hey, you ever seen a nard explode?
A... a what? A wha... a nard?
I don't...
Is that something on the Internet?
Uh, 'cause I...
Ah, damn it, what the hell?!
Oh, nice shot there.
Come on, don't get mad, bro.
I was just kidding.
You were kidding?!
What was the joke?!
This was!
Oh, damn it, you hit the seam!
Oh!
Yeah.
You know what?
You're a jerk, Gronk!
That's it,
I'm getting rid of that bastard.
Just like I helped kick the British
out of America.
This tyranny shall not stand!
For without liberty...
Ah, crap, he's even in the cutaways!
Just...
Just go to commercial.
I'm gonna squat here
and hold onto this bench.
Peter, you got to figure something out.
They haven't stopped
partying the whole night.
- Yeah!
- Gronk!
- Party!
- I'm the dad!
I'm sorry, you were right all along.
But don't worry, I'll take care of it.
Well, you better do something soon.
I can't live like this.
I know. That guy's more annoying
than going to an Italian restaurant
with someone who's been to Italy.
They call this a trattoria?
More like a ristorante to me.
Look at that fresco.
Supposed to be the hills of Elba?
Not once you've seen 'em.
Are you ready to order?
Si. Let me handle this, Peter.
Two spaghettis and a chicken fingers.
God, look at all the
honey the bees made!
Those steroids were
a great idea, Stewie.
Hey, look, that bee is
trying to get our honey.
Okay, Mr. Bee,
we'll give you the employee discount.
After all, you...
Holy crap!
That thing just lifted
a whole jar of honey!
Oh, God, do you think that's
one of our steroid bees?
Well, this one's wearing
a hoodie as a shirt.
So, yeah, I think these are ours.
Stewie, I have a bad feeling abo...
Oh, God, it just ate the other bee!
Okay, so a few of them
had a bad reaction to...
Oh, crap.
Oh, my God. Brian, run!
I think maybe giving those bees steroids
was a bad idea.
Turn on the wipers!
You sure this is gonna work, Peter?
Absolutely.
Gronk went to the University of Arizona,
and everyone who went to
the University of Arizona
believes leprechauns are real.
And since Cleveland already owns
a green suit and a top hat...
This is my Easter clothes.
Whoa, a leprechaun!
Say the thing.
Top
of the morning to you,
Mr. Gronkowski.
Have you any interest in a pot of gold?
All you have to do is
move to Tallahassee!
Wait a minute,
this is just a disguise!
Aah, son of a bitch!
What's going on here?
Are you guys trying to get rid of me?
Yeah, we're tryin' to get rid of you!
Why?
'Cause you're a pain in
the ass to live next to!
I mean, what the hell, Gronk?
Why you got to be like this?
You're a millionaire,
you have the sweetest job in the world,
you can do whatever you want.
Why you got to act like
such an idiot all the time?
It's not a choice, Grover.
But rather, an obligation.
You see, I've been groomed for this
my entire life.
Scoring touchdowns,
making people laugh,
punishing my body,
enduring the pain.
All in the name of entertainment.
Don't you understand?
I'm a commodity, a product.
A modern day gladiator.
You ask about the
whys and the wherefores
behind the boorish facade?
The answer is simple:
I play the jester because
society deems it necessary.
Also, I'm insane!
Eat a butt, fatty!
Gronk ain't going nowhere!
Oh, that's it!
Oh, cool, we're fighting?
You guys mind if I eat
while I beat you up?
What the hell are we supposed to do?
We're surrounded!
Hang on, I got this.
"Meg, come outside.
We have Pinkberry."
Ow! Ow, ow! Stop... stop it!
All right, they're distracted,
let's go!
Quick! We just have to
get rid of the queen!
She's in the hive!
What's that gonna do?
The bees instinctively
stay with the queen,
so if she's gone, they'll follow her!
Okay, great, but how we gonna do it?
You guys are bad fighters.
That's his third sub.
Ah, cool!
Honey rain!
Aah, oh, my God,
is that a bee?!
You have bees here?
Uh, yeah, it's the world.
Holy crap!
There's a ton of them!
Dad, start up the party bus!
We're moving!
Bees?
Yeah, bees!
And they're showing blitz!
We got to leave on two!
You think their Wi-Fi is "Vag-Town"?
Yeah, that's probably them.
Look at that, no password.
Oh, well, thank goodness
we finally have our neighborhood back.
Yeah, now maybe Wilson
can move back in and
give me homespun wisdom over the fence.
Peter, that was Home Improvement.
It's exhausting
that you never just go
with something I say.
Coming up, yesterday's brisket.
But first, breaking news:
Rob Gronkowski has been
suspended from the Patriots
following a failed drug test
that showed evidence of
steroids in his system.
The star athlete claims he has no idea
how the banned substance
got into his body.
Oh, no way!
That's terrible.
When pressed for further comment,
Mr. Gronkowski said simply,
"Grover, go long."
Uh-oh.
Thank you for watching "Family Guy" on
www.FOX-fan.ru